

Brendan Lane Branding + Graphic Designer

778-229-6480 lane.bmc@gmail.com www.brendan-lane.com

About Me

I'm a branding and graphic designer from beautiful Vancouver, British Columbia, with a passion for helping others express themselves in a meaningful way. My bread n' butter is helping others tell the story of themselves or of their company, and I'm driven by a desire for great user experiences and human-centered design.

Skills

Illustrator Photoshop InDesign

After Effects HTML + CSS
Premiere Pro Wordpress
Microsoft Office SmartGit

Axure RP Proto.io

Selected Experience

Brendan Lane Design / Freelance Graphic and Brand Designer

May 2013 - Present brendan-lane.com

Designed brands and graphic material for clients such as photography startup Vanvero, Richmond Chinese Alliance Church, and Carnarvon Community School. Created logos, posters, and other media to unify branding across web and print.

nwHacks / Graphic Designer

November 2015 - February 2016 2016.nwhacks.io/

Designed all of the promotional and day-of graphic material for nwHacks, the largest hackathon in Western Canada, including sponsorship booklets, banners, and t-shirts. Collaborated with the hackathon team to develop a unified visual brand.

BCcampus / Production Assistant

May 2014 - July 2016 bccampus.ca/open-textbook-project/

Developed responsive, accessible textbooks to be used in BC open education. Assisted with photography at ETUG 2014 and videography at the BCOER 2014 event, generating multimedia awareness surrounding open education in British Columbia.

Education

Simon Fraser University / School of Interactive Arts and Technology, BA in Design September 2010 - April 2016 ww.siat.sfu.ca

Graduated with First Class with Distinction honours.